Performing Minimum Vertex Cover Approximation...
Visiting vertex: D, Visisted = {D}
     Updating degree of vertex A to 3
     Updating degree of vertex B to 2
     Updating degree of vertex E to 2
     Updating degree of vertex G to 2
     Updating degree of vertex F to 3

Visiting vertex: A, Visisted = {D,A}
     Updating degree of vertex C to 1
     Updating degree of vertex B to 1
     Updating degree of vertex F to 2

Visiting vertex: E, Visisted = {D,A,E}
     Updating degree of vertex B to 0
     Updating degree of vertex G to 1

Visiting vertex: F, Visisted = {D,A,E,F}
     Updating degree of vertex C to 0
     Updating degree of vertex G to 0

VERTEX COVER = D,A,E,F
